[{"answer": "Regardless of whatever he's going to do.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Regardless of his capacity?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's very fair for the family of Trayvon Martin to be asking the question why George Zimmerman wasn't arrested.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What is your overview as we sit here tonight of this case?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, we're not clear on whether he's been arrested or not.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Tell me this, why is he seen in handcuffs if he hasn't been arrested?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "How significant will that be to this debate, Charles, if that is true?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, there in lies the rub as Shakespeare might have said, because after all, we don't know what the exact facts are.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What do you think of the \"Stand Your Ground\" law in relation to this case?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "There may very well be.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Would you imagine, Gloria, very quickly, that there will be an arrest and indictment very soon in relation to George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't think it's going to be any sooner than five days or so.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Mark Geragos, would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "My instinct as just a citizen, I'm not a professional like Geragos and Allred, I remember first hearing about it and hearing Zimmerman on the phone.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "In this situation, I don't think it's a case of working on either/or in our society.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "What do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "If I shot Justin Bieber, would I be out tonight?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "He's 12.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "How old is your son?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "He's Arsenio Jr., right?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "I'm totally confused.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What do you say to him post-Trayvon Martin about walking on his own now?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Well, I think the scariest thing was when you get there and they take your phone and give you one.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "How did you find it?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Yes, it's amazing.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Did you ever imagine the day would come where you'd have Magic Johnson owner of the Dodgers and Barack Obama president of the United States in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "At Peter Max's house.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Where is that jacket?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "That was one of the reasons I really thought this book should be written, is that most people really didn't know her, including members of the press who actually covered her during that period of time.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "What was she really like?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "ILL: They were very close, very much in love.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "How did they get on when the door was closed and they were left with just agents like you who saw everything?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, I had a great deal of concern about their welfare and well being.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "And you're witnessing such private moments of great joy and great despair?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Well, that never really leaves my consciousness.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Clint, whenever you see those images, those images, what do you feel so long after that event?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Is that's what's going through your mind?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "After I got up on the car and Mrs. Kennedy came up on the trunk to retrieve some material that had gone off to the right rear from the president's wound in his head, I put her back in the seat.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "When did you realize that the president was probably dead?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, I've always felt a sense of guilt.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "How has that responsibility borne down on you over the years since then?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, I went back to Dallas in 1990.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "When you look back on that, is there anything you could have done?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "At that time, there were 34 assigned to the president.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "How many people were on the detail that day?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "She was in shock.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Was she able to speak to you at all?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Do you believe Lee Harvey Oswald was just a man acting alone?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "We had some wonderful times.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What's your favorite of your time with her?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Katherine, how are you?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "I can't quite believe what's happening to you.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Can you believe what's going on here?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "ENKINS: It is funny because, you know, when I have been here before to make albums, it's been pretty much sort of under the radar.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Is it weird to be over here now with this huge army of new fans who think that Katherine Jenkins, great dancer?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "It's hard work, but it's fun.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Are you having fun or is it incredibly hard work?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "No, he's got a girlfriend.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Is he single?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "It has been.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Yes, because it's been a bit of a tough time for you, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "Just, like you said, this is something to me that feels like really old news.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "What do you want to say about it?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Honestly, it would be going out to entertain the troops in Afghanistan and Iraq.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "What's been the big high for you professionally outside of what's going on now?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What's going on here?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "ENKINS: Well, I think, you know, singing has always been my big passion in life.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Is that the ultimate Holy Grail for any big singer now, do you think?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Oh, well, you know, I hope that he would be -- he would be happy and proud.", "docId": "120405pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "What do you think he would make of his little girl now conquering America on the dance floor?", "qSentId": 621}]